<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<androidx.core.widget.NestedScrollView
    xmlns:android="http://schemas.android.com/apk/res/android"
    xmlns:app="http://schemas.android.com/apk/res-auto"
    android:layout_width="match_parent"
    android:layout_height="match_parent">
    <LinearLayout
        android:layout_width="match_parent"
        android:layout_height="match_parent"
        android:orientation="horizontal">

        <!-- Add your popup content here -->
        <!-- Example: TextView -->
        <com.google.android.material.card.MaterialCardView
            android:id="@+id/view_newsCard"
            android:layout_width="match_parent"
            android:layout_height="match_parent"
            android:layout_gravity="center">
            <LinearLayout
                android:layout_width="wrap_content"
                android:layout_height="wrap_content"
                android:orientation="vertical"
                android:padding="20dp">
                <TextView
                    android:id="@+id/textViewTitle"
                    android:layout_width="match_parent"
                    android:layout_height="wrap_content"
                    android:text="Antwerp Governor Commends Sri Lanka’s Initiatives to Tackle Climate Change"
                    android:textSize="20dp"
                    android:textStyle="bold"/>
                <TextView
                    android:id="@+id/textViewInformation"
                    android:layout_width="match_parent"
                    android:layout_height="wrap_content"
                    android:text="Sri Lanka - 2023-12-28"
                    android:textColor="@color/light_grey"/>
                <TextView
                    android:id="@+id/textViewDetails"
                    android:layout_width="match_parent"
                    android:layout_height="wrap_content"
                    android:text="Governor of Antwerp, Belgium Cathy Berx, and Head of Mission to the European Union for Sri Lanka Ambassador Grace Asirwatham, engaged in a discussion on the efforts taken to combat climate change by both national and international stakeholders. The meeting took place at the Governor’s office on 21 December 2023 in Antwerp. The Ambassador was accompanied by the Honorary Consul of Sri Lanka in Antwerp Monique De Deker, and Second Secretary of the Embassy of Sri Lanka Dulmini Dahanayake.\n\nGovernor Berx highlighted Antwerp’s recognized environmental consciousness within Belgium, citing its strategic position and commitment to sustainable practices. She underscored the significance of Antwerp as a hub for sustainability initiatives, emphasizing its role in shaping Belgium's broader environmental agenda.\n\nAmbassador Asirwatham provided insights into Sri Lanka's Climate Prosperity Plan, designed with a primary focus on achieving sustainable economic growth through climate resilience. The Ambassador added that the plan sets strategic aims, including transforming Sri Lanka into a low-carbon hub and elevating renewable energy generation from 35% to 70% by 2030, aligning with the Paris Agreement's goals to limit global warming to 1.5 degrees Celsius.\n\nFurthermore, the Ambassador shared Sri Lanka's ambitious proposal to establish an International Climate Change University, promoting global collaboration in climate-related research and technologies for the collective benefit of humanity.\n\nGovernor Berx commended Sri Lanka's commitment to sustainable practices and its notable achievements in combating climate change. She expressed admiration for Sri Lanka's holistic approach, which encompasses renewable energy targets and innovative strategies to reduce carbon emissions across various sectors. Governor Berx acknowledged Sri Lanka's active participation and valuable contributions to global climate initiatives.\n\nThe meeting also served as an occasion for the Governor to bid farewell to Ambassador Asirwatham. The Governor expressed appreciation for the Ambassador's significant role in strengthening the ties between the Embassy of Sri Lanka and the city of Antwerp, which is the principal port city in Belgium.\n\nEmbassy of Sri Lanka\n\nBrussels\n\n28 December 2023"
                    android:textSize="17dp"/>

                <Button
                    android:layout_marginTop="10dp"
                    android:layout_marginBottom="10dp"
                    android:id="@+id/button_back"
                    android:layout_width="match_parent"
                    android:layout_height="wrap_content"
                    android:text="Back" />

            </LinearLayout>

        </com.google.android.material.card.MaterialCardView>


        <!-- Add other UI elements as needed -->

    </LinearLayout>
</androidx.core.widget.NestedScrollView>